
var myFlashcards = [     {question:"hindsight a no no",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>dance</b></span></a>'},{question:"judicial notice",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-2400-networking-mulitplexing.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Ahlert and Knapp-Monarch</b></span></a>'},{question:"structure not purpose",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-2400-networking-mulitplexing.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Catalina</b></span></a>'},{question:"motivation to combine",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_06.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ball aerosol</b></span></a>'},{question:"if your attorney screws up, it's your fault...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_09.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>pioneer</b></span></a>'},{question:"claims not embodiments define scope",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_10.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>permahedge</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness gotta say why and gotta come from prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_11.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>dance perfectweb vaidyanahan ksr</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness requires more that bunch of separate references covering each limitation in claim...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-3600-transportation.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>unigene</b></span></a>'},{question:"removeably secured means screws",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/01/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_30.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>K-2</b></span></a>'},{question:"unexpected results",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>heyna, mcclain, passal, lohr</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim can't include both obvious and non-obvious subject matter...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>muchmore</b></span></a>'},{question:"admissions in spec affect obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_04.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>pharmastem</b></span></a>'},{question:"cost no problem for POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_08.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>farrenkopf</b></span></a>'},{question:"catalysts treated differently in 103 combinations",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_14.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kerhkoven, yates</b></span></a>'},{question:"burden of proof in product by process is less",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_14.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fessman</b></span></a>'},{question:"don't have to believe one expert over another",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_15.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>rohm and haas v. brotech</b></span></a>'},{question:"picking and choosing ok in a 103 rejection",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_22.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>arkley</b></span></a>'},{question:"Obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_29.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Detroit Iron Works</b></span></a>'},{question:"Obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_22.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>velander</b></span></a>'},{question:"prima facie case for obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_30.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kao</b></span></a>'},{question:"two elements cannot be one and the same",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>gaus, unique concepts, netmoneyin</b></span></a>'},{question:"combination doesn't include how to combine",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nievelt</b></span></a>'},{question:"long felt but unsolved need not just need in isolation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_18.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>monarch knitting</b></span></a>'},{question:"must be nonobvious to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dann</b></span></a>'},{question:"chemical secondary considerations",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_25.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>cescon</b></span></a>'},{question:"old cases for taking judicial notice, common knowledge",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_26.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>chevenard, boon</b></span></a>'},{question:"J. Rich case, obvious cannot be predicated on what is unknown",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sporman</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness requres more than showing references cover limitations",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>unigene</b></span></a>'},{question:"making something separable is obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dulberg</b></span></a>'},{question:"patent office must provide factual basis in 103",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_07.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>warner</b></span></a>'},{question:"(J. Rich 1988) for obvious to try needs reasonable expectation of success",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_08.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>OFarrell</b></span></a>'},{question:"not in mpep can't use claimed invention as instruction manual to piece together teachings of prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_09.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>fritch</b></span></a>'},{question:"reference is available for all it discloses to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/affirmed-in-part-2629-ex-parte-jeong.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lamberti</b></span></a>'},{question:"teaching away needs more than just differences",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-2800-semiconductors-electrical_16.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>beattie</b></span></a>'},{question:"seperation of elements obvious only if for a reason",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_17.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>dulberg</b></span></a>'},{question:"failure to address evidence is error",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_21.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sullivan</b></span></a>'},{question:"old chief judge markey case that removal of part but keeping its function is obvious is not per se rule",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_24.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>edge</b></span></a>'},{question:"nature of problem to be solved can provide motivation to combine",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_25.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Princeton, Dystar</b></span></a>'},{question:"businessman is same as person of ordinary skill",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_30.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>farrenkopf</b></span></a>'},{question:"Inherency",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mehl</b></span></a>'},{question:"new J. Rader case obviousness analysis requires amnesia",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mintz</b></span></a>'},{question:"C.J. Radar for obviousness "common sense" no good without support",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_07.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mintz</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI does not include giving claims a legally incorrect interpretation solely an examination expedient, not a rule of claim construction.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_11.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>In re Skvorecz</b></span></a>'},{question:"choosing species out of genus not necessarily obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_13.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>jones, lemin, merck</b></span></a>'},{question:"secondary considerations need nexus to ovecome prima facie case of obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_13.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wyers, kao</b></span></a>'},{question:"Obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and_19.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>leapfrog and ksr</b></span></a>'},{question:"significance of shapes must be disclosed in spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_20.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>dailey</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness is fact specific",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_21.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>howard</b></span></a>'},{question:"genus specie",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baird and jones</b></span></a>'},{question:"prima facie case",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hedges</b></span></a>'},{question:"non-obvious if combination doesn't work",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mcginley</b></span></a>'},{question:"death ray is obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-3600-transportation.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>optivus</b></span></a>'},{question:"wikipedia not reliable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/mobile-search-reversed-2100-computer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>techradium</b></span></a>'},{question:"teaching away must suggest unlikely to work",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-3600-transportation_09.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>baxter int'l</b></span></a>'},{question:"combining two embodiments next to each other in same prior art not inventive",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/mobile-search-reversed-1600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>boston scientific</b></span></a>'},{question:"expected beneficial results are evidence of obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/mobile-search-reversed-1600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>skoner</b></span></a>'},{question:"for analogous art construed broadly",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wyers</b></span></a>'},{question:"Judge Rader for hindsight",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-1700-chemical-materials.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rouffet</b></span></a>'},{question:"when picking and choosing certain elements from various prior art have to show suggestion or motivation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>interconnect</b></span></a>'},{question:"need to identify result effective variable for ranges",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-2400-networking.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>antonie</b></span></a>'},{question:"Hindsight",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-2400-networking.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>grain processing</b></span></a>'},{question:"ranges in chemical context",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1600_23.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>boesch and sebek</b></span></a>'},{question:"combinations and TSM",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_24.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gartside and dembiczak</b></span></a>'},{question:"combinations don't require actual physical substitution of elements",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_24.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>moutette and etter</b></span></a>'},{question:"preferred embodiment in prior art not controlling",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1700-chemical_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lamberti, merck</b></span></a>'},{question:"wikipedia unreliable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1700-chemical_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>techradium</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness rejection examiner can't just make conclusory statements",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1700-chemical_30.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>vaidyanathan</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness combination doesn't require physical substitution",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1700-chemical_31.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mouttet</b></span></a>'},{question:"post KSR no formalistic rules for obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-1600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Kubin</b></span></a>'},{question:"combinations have to have reasonable expectation of success",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-1600_10.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>apotex and reinhart</b></span></a>'},{question:"secondary considerations",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-1600_10.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sud-chemie</b></span></a>'},{question:"103 overturned interesting remand from fed circuit",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-1600_13.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kao</b></span></a>'},{question:"AIA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-3600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>loughlin</b></span></a>'},{question:"need fair opportunity to respond",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-2100.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>leithem</b></span></a>'},{question:"no objective indicia of non-obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-2100.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>mintz</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness requires more than separate references",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-2800.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>unigene</b></span></a>'},{question:"was just location of a switch not multiple differences in combination of references",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_22.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>japiske</b></span></a>'},{question:"no per se rule of unpatentability",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_22.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ochiai</b></span></a>'},{question:"each case has it's own merits",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>gyurik</b></span></a>'},{question:"reversal not a mandate for issuance",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>voss</b></span></a>'},{question:"103 have to explain reasoning",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600_28.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>lee</b></span></a>'},{question:"combined prior art reasonably expected to maintain respective property or function after combined",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-3600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sundance</b></span></a>'},{question:"only notice of facts that defy disput",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ahlert, knapp monarch</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness compound and its properties the same",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-2100.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>papesch</b></span></a>'},{question:"analogous art two prong test, within field of inventor's endevor and if not, reasonably pertinent to problem involved - logially would have commended itself to inventor's attention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-3700.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wood, clay</b></span></a>'},{question:"if property affected the variable it is a result effective variable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_21.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>applied materials</b></span></a>'},{question:"desirability not most desirable for combination being obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600_25.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fulton, beattie, winner international</b></span></a>'},{question:"for hindsight",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_26.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>monarch</b></span></a>'},{question:"for mere duplication of parts",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/09/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_26.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>st. regis</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness cannot be predicated on what is unknown",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rijckaert</b></span></a>'},{question:"for examiner has to cite reference to support rejection",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/hoch.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hoch</b></span></a>'},{question:"ornament not enough",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/falkner-lizardtech-seid.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>seid</b></span></a>'},{question:"the words common sense add nothing",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/bozek-mintz-perfect-web-paperless.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>perfect web, bozek, mintz</b></span></a>'},{question:"optimization of ranges obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/aller-arkley-borkowski-dreyfus-fisher.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>aller, dreyfus, waite</b></span></a>'},{question:"for unexpected results need only be between closest prior art and invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/baxter-chapman-nuijten-greenfield.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baxter travenol, chapman, burckel</b></span></a>'},{question:"in nonstatutory double patenting the earlier app is not available for a 103 rejection",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/baxter-chapman-nuijten-greenfield.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>general foods</b></span></a>'},{question:"unexpected results needs more than a few data points to be commensurate in scope with claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/baxter-chapman-nuijten-greenfield.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>greenfield, tiffin, kollman</b></span></a>'},{question:"secondary considerations can't overcome strong 103",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/media-techs-nuijten-tiffin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>media tech</b></span></a>'},{question:"commercial success must be commensurate with the claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/media-techs-nuijten-tiffin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>tiffin</b></span></a>'},{question:"on a slow day...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/ksr.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>KSR</b></span></a>'}
     ];
